hey everybody this is Jeff from canal
sound I like coming back to you with
another product video today we have the
adj on tour chill
[Music]
the adj ant or chill is a new low-lying
fog machine with a brand new developed
800 watt heating system that allows for
continuous output for up to an hour
it has a fast warmup time of only three
minutes and the new electronic
temperature control allows you to fire
it at any given time the the unit uses
ice and dense fog fluid it has a 5 pound
ice chamber right here for regular ice
not dry ice and also a 1 liter tank
right here to hold the fog fluid and
preferably a DJ's cool fog fluid which
is a dense fog fluid this unit is about
seventeen and a half pounds and very
portable as you can see in comparison to
some of the bigger units out there that
are like 70 to 80 pounds and require two
power sources the adj ontour chill is a
nice portable easy to use unit for a lot
of those quinceañeras weddings low-lying
fog effects and concerts or haunted
effects and things like that on the back
you will find an indicator of how much
fluid you have in the tank
it'll also flash from red to green to
show when it's ready you have a 16
character LCD that that a lot gives you
the menu it has DMX it has a spot for a
remote timer remote and it also has a
place where you can drain the excess
fluid and it comes with both the tube
and the bag that holds the excess fluid
as you can see so right now we're going
to demo the ontour chill everybody we're
gonna check out the on tour chill where
it's normally used on the ground so this
would be perfect for a stage for a
dancefloor or any haunted occasion
as you can see it immediately fires it
only warms up and as I mentioned in
three minutes so this is a great
alternative to your other dry ice
effects which we would require dry ice
front for for it to work or like extra
power and some of these units require
multiple power sources so the adj ontour
chill is a great new low-lying fog
machine an affordable price of only 399
and it's very portable as you can see
and it's a very low requirements very
low maintenance all it needs is ice and
fog fluid and it's great for any
production company theater event company
or like a haunted attraction at home you
could use it for your your haunted house
so it's a very cool effect this is Jeff
thanks for watching please like and
subscribe our our video check us out on
Instagram as well or at Canal sound
light and we're looking forward to
seeing you in the next video thank you
you